

 $\square$ 

igypap@gmail.com



+48 504 781 817

#### AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- JAVA
- Spring
- SQL
- Maven
- Docker

## **SECTORS**

- Financial
- · Derivatives Market
- Consulting
- Insurance

## EDUCATION & CERTIFICATES

- Master's Degree in Electrical Engineering at Kielce University of Technology graduation date: 2012
- Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering at Kielce University of Technology graduation date: 2010

### LANGUAGES

- Polish
- English

# Igor Paprzycki

Senior Java developer / Technical Lead

## **Profile**

Igor is Senior Java developer with overall of 11 years of experience in the area related to software development.

He has demonstrated proficiency in leading teams through the integration of reusable components, designing and developing generic application components in microservices architecture, and contributing to the creation of a data streaming platform for Risk Management Services.

Igor's extensive experience includes stakeholder interaction throughout the software lifecycle, from design and development to release and support.

## Project experience

## PWC - JULY 2021 - PRESENT

Played a leading technical role in the technical domain, overseeing a project focused on integrating reusable components across various clients. Designed and developed generic and reusable application components within a microservices architecture, catering to multiple clients.

Tech stack: JAVA 17, Spring, SQL Server, Docker, Kubernetes, Azure DevOps, NodeJS

## CITI BANK - FEBRUARY 2020 - JUNE 2021

Pioneered the development of a data streaming platform using Apache Flink for Risk Management Services, showcasing expertise in cutting-edge technologies.

Tech stack: JAVA, Spring, Apache Kafka, Apache Flink

## Pragmasoft / PZU - MAY 2018 - FEBRUARY 2020

Developed a web-based application for claim submission, contributing to the efficiency of microservices infrastructure. Tech stack: **JAVA**, **TypeScript**, **Spring**, **Hibernate**, **Soap**, **PostgreSQL**, **Docker** 

## Goldman Sachs - JUNE 2017 - APRIL 2018

Design and developed Clearing House communication API for internal trade and clearing processing in the Derivatives market, ensuring seamless and secure transactions.

Tech stack: JAVA, Spring, Apache Kafka, Hibernate, DB2

## Previous experience - SINCE 2013

Previous experience includes freelance software development and engineering work related to design and commissioning of a Fan Blade Out facility for aviation engines testing centre.

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).